<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>State on Truslavistan State News Archive</title>
    <link>https://truslav.com/articles/categories/state/</link>
    <description>Recent content in State on Truslavistan State News Archive</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>The Ministry of Current Happenings</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 16:27:52 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://truslav.com/articles/categories/state/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PROGRESS STALLS IN BANDWIDTH CRISIS</title>
      <link>https://truslav.com/articles/post/progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 16:27:52 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truslav.com/articles/post/progress/</guid>
      <description>MONDAY – After an accidental leak of classified information by erroneous ex-journalist Papov Pavokovish in last week’s publication,
mass shortages of bandwidth were observed to have occurred on the People’s Wireless after the top secret password was published for all to see.
With the normal leaks of top secret information resulting in instant death under the hoofs of a hundred hungry swine,
Pavokovish received a lighter sentence after saying he was, in essence, “giving interwebs to the peoples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PANIC AFTER WIRELESS NETWORK FAILS</title>
      <link>https://truslav.com/articles/post/panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 16:17:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truslav.com/articles/post/panic/</guid>
      <description>FRIDAY – In what many would call the “darkest days since root vegetable famine,” the country is tested as the wireless network fails across all of Truslavistan, crippling the new economy set-up by Petrov Manishlakov last week,
from his house. The general unease of the nation can be felt for kilometers, with some destabilizing underneath the pressure.
Ljudevit Snizdivzic, age 49, was seen two days ago running naked, covered in mud, through the back village streets shouting nonsense and making bizarre animal noises all throughout the night like he does every Wednesday, showing that mental strength still prevails among the public in these dire times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECONOMIC BOOM AS FIRST TECH BUSINESS BEGINS IN TRUSLAVISTAN</title>
      <link>https://truslav.com/articles/post/economic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 16:05:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://truslav.com/articles/post/economic/</guid>
      <description>THURSDAY – In what many are considering a breakthrough moment for the micronation of Truslavistan, the people’s country has birthed a modern tech miracle. After years of research, trial-and-error, Petrov Manishlakov has managed to start the first-ever online business from his state-issued apartment in the downtown square.
“I was ready to give up,” Manishlakov admits, “until that shining moment occurred at 3 in the morning and my breakthrough happened.” Manishlakov sits, beaming with pride, near his computer set-up.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>